1iota.com 2007-12-29

# 1iota.com - event tickets, tv, late night, jimmy kimmel, carson daly, last call, abc, nbc

**_Introduction_ **_(last updated on 08/23/2005)_  
The Privacy Policy below will govern your 1iota membership and any information you provide on this site. In order to become a member of 1iota we must ask you to provide us with information about yourself. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect and how we use that information. 1iota takes the privacy of your personal information very seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

1iota is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site 

_www.1iota.com_. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Courtney at [support@1iota.com](mailto:support@1iota.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or you inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php> TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

_  
**Changes of Policy** _  
This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to 1iota or as we incorporate new suggestions from our members. If we are going to use or disclose your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time we collected the information, you will be notified by email or by means of a notice on our homepage. 1iota may make improvements and/or changes in our services or products described in the site, including the terms and conditions of your use of this site, without liability. 1iota reserves the right to change these conditions at anytime.

**_Required Information_**  
When you register for an account with our site you will be asked for your contact information such as first and last name, typGenre, birthday, city, state and zip code. In order to become a basic member of 1iota, you must provide this information to us. A user can access their submitted information and make changes at anytime on the “my basic account info” section of the site. A user’s last name cannot be altered on the site due to members’ attempts to transfer e-tickets as our e-tickets are non-transferable. To alter your last name, please send an email to [support@1iota.com](mailto:support@1iota.com?Subject=Account%20Name%20Change). A user can also cancel their membership at any time by visiting the “resign your account” section of the site.   
**  
_Optional Information_**  
Our site offers users the ability to set up an optional casting profile, under the “my casting info” section of the site. Information included in this profile pertains to users' personal attributes, interests, and preferences, such as, ethnicity, hair color, eye color, height, weight and special skills. Our site also offers users the ability to submit and store photos of themselves, under the “my photo” section of the site. Our site offers users the ability to receive wireless updates by entering your wireless number on the “my wireless alerts section” of the site and checking the “please send 1iota updates and information box.” Our site offers users the ability to receive emails from the site regarding upcoming events and event updates. A user can opt-out of receiving emails by clicking the “please send me 1iota event updates and info” on the “my email preferences” section of the site. If you choose to use our referral service to email a friend about an upcoming event, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. 1iota does not store this information.

**_Customer Feedback_**  
We encourage you to share your comments and questions with us. We promise to read all the mail that is sent to us, but we may not be able to respond to it all. We will retain such information in the records of your membership. We retain these records in order to measure and improve our customer service. We may, over time, delete these records if permitted by law. 

**_Use and Disclosure_**  
We use the information we collect about you in order 1) to provide membership services, 2) to determine your eligibility to be selected for special events and shows, and 3) to operate our site efficiently and continue to improve our membership relations and services.

**_Disclosure to Third Parties_**  
1iota will not share any of your personally identifiable information with third parties except in the limited circumstances described below.   
1\. If selected for a show, 1iota will be authorized to use the information provided, to grant you access to the event and take the proper security precautions required by event staff or security (such as background checks). Background checks will only be done when attending a national security event, which will be specified in the event description. A background check will take place upon registering for that event by the respected government agency.

2\. We share names with affiliated nightclubs for guest-list options or table reservations, upon taking advantage of the "1iota nightlife" feature.

3\. We use contact information to send the user information needed to maintain their account, to contact them when necessary, and to notify them of news about our company. We also use customer contact information to send the user promotional material from some of our partners.

4\. **Service Providers:** We use 800-HOSTING to provide website hosting on our site. When you sign up for a basic membership with 1iota, we will share your “Required Information” and any “optional Information” as necessary for 800-HOSTING to provide that service. 

5\. We share aggregated statistical data with our business partners or for public relations. We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors. However, these statistics will not include personal identifying information.

6\. Account information may be released when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to: (1) comply with applicable law; (2) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements; or (3) protect the rights, property or safety of our users and/or any third parties.

7\. As with any other business, it is possible that in the future 1iota could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by 1 iota, including customer account information, but would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy unless and until it is amended as described above in the "Changes of Policy" section. 

8\. Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms: If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of members who use these services in a manner inconsistent with our Terms & Conditions (link).

9\. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

**_Cookies_**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We do use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies for authentication purposes and we use persistent cookies only to remember user names not passwords. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We set a persistent cookie to store your desScreenName, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. To remove a persistent cookie, uncheck the “remember me” box on the log in screen. If you reject cookies, you may still visit our site, but your ability to login will be limited.

**_Security_**  
1iota is committed to handling your membership information with a high standard of security. The security of your 1iota membership also relies on your protection of your 1 iota password/Id number. We strongly urge that you never share your 1iota password/Id number with anyone. You will only be asked for your 1iota password/ID number if you are logging in as a user. If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password, please change it immediately or request it to be changed by [contacting us](mailto:support@1iota.com?Subject=Password%20Change). These guidelines are the only understanding and agreement we have regarding your use of the site. The laws of the State of California govern these guidelines.

**_Contact Info_**  
1iota productions LLC  
6834 Hollywood Blvd.  
Hollywood, CA 90028
